naijajobslink.com 2016-06-05

# Privacy Policy - NaijaJobsLink - Job Vacancies and Career Opportunities in Nigeria

Overview

NaijaJobsLink is committed to respecting and protecting your personal information. We strive to provide a safe and secure experience to all visitors, job seekers and customers of NaijaJobsLink.com (together with all sites owned or operated by NaijaJobsLink, collectively called the “Site”).

This Privacy Policy is intended to clarify treatment of any personal information collected from you while visiting NaijaJobsLink.com. This Privacy Policy also describes the online data collection and usage policies and practices of NaijaJobsLink.com and is not applicable to information we collect in any other fashion.

Please note, information you post in public areas of the Site or information you provide and make public during the registration, profile completion, and apply process may be accessed, used, and stored by others. While our goal is to provide a safe and secure environment, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access to your information, so you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information to NaijaJobsLink.com.

Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use and other published guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information about our members or visitors without their permission.

By clicking the “Register” button during the registration process or by using this Site, you explicitly accept the collection and use of personal information, provided by you, in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information on NaijaJobsLink.com, we recommend that you do not visit the Site or use any of its related services.

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. Each time you visit the site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://naijajobslink.com/contact/).

Collection and Use of Information by NaijaJobsLink.com

In certain areas of NaijaJobsLink.com, such as those in which you register, complete a profile, apply to a job posting, create a new account, or enter a NaijaJobsLink.com contest or promotion, we may request that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, telephone number, resume, credit card number, address, billing information, and other personal information from which your identity may be discernible. You may always choose not to provide such personally identifiable information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or particular content.

In other areas of the Site, we collect or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you, including your age, gender, profession, and ZIP code.

We also collect or may collect information about your use of NaijaJobsLink.com, including what areas of the Site you visit, what services you access and what links or advertisements you click on. Moreover, we may collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include your browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet Service Provider, access times, and referring website addresses. While we may be able to determine your geographic location from this information, it is not linked to your personal information.

From time to time we may provide you with the opportunity to submit behavioural, descriptive, cultural, preferential, and/or lifestyle information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you choose to furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you thereby give your consent to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. For example, such information may be used to determine if you are interested in receiving e-mail or other communications about particular products or services.

If you choose to use our online reference service to request a personal or professional reference statement, we may ask you to provide the name and e-mail address of an individual/s. We will automatically send this individual a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit NaijaJobsLink.com to provide a reference statement that will be associated with your profile. We do not store this information.

How We Use Your Information

We use the personal, demographic, collective, and/or technical information we gather on NaijaJobsLink.com for the purpose of operating and improving NaijaJobsLink.com, creating a positive user experience, and to deliver the products and services that we offer.

We may use your contact information to send you email or other communications regarding NaijaJobsLink.com updates, or to solicit your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services. We may also send you promotions, communications, or other information on NaijaJobsLink.com opportunities and additional job postings which according to your user information we believe may be of interest to you. The frequency and nature of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you.

If you have given your consent, the information we gather may be used by us to inform you of other products or services available from us or from our affiliated companies.

In addition, we may send you free informational newsletters related to topics that may be of special interest to you, including career advice.

NaijaJobsLink.com includes areas where you can submit advice, feedback or comments. Information you submit in these areas becomes our property, and we may contact you for further information or use such advice, feedback or comments for marketing purposes. We may also delete such information at anytime as desired by us.

Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties, or your combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of NaijaJobsLink.com (including the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth below.

  1. We disclose information if requested to do so by a governmental entity, if legally required to do so, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (b) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (c) protect the personal safety of users or the public; or (d) prevent a crime or protect national security.
  2. We disclose information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if at the time you register with NaijaJobsLink.com, you state that you would like to receive information about products, opportunities, or services of third parties, we may supply your contact information to third parties including but not limited to data aggregators, employers, recruiters, marketers, and/or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We use data we have about you (such as the skills, professional experience and preferences you have expressed) to determine whether you might want to receive information about the products, opportunities, or services of a particular third party.
  3. We will transfer and/or disclose your information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of consolidation, merger, or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In the event we become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, either we or our trustees in bankruptcy may license, sell, or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. You will be notified of any sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party via e-mail or through a public notice posted on NaijaJobsLink.com.
  4. We may, from time to time, disclose information to companies and individuals we contract to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include, but are not limited to, analyzing data, processing credit card payments, hosting our web servers, providing marketing assistance, and/or providing customer service. These individuals and companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their designated functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party.

Other Uses of Information

We may share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to NaijaJobsLink.com with partners, advertisers, clients, and other third parties. We may also aggregate, on an anonymous basis, data regarding education, age, job qualifications, experience level, or other information relevant to the competition or job search among seekers for any such job. Such data may be made available to other job seekers or employers.

If you apply to a job posted on NaijaJobsLink.com, where permitted by applicable law, you may be asked to provide information on your race, gender, or other protected status. For reporting and record-keeping requirements, some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants. If provided, this information will be used by employers only in accordance with applicable law and will not be used in making negative employment decisions. All race, gender, or other protected status information will be kept separate from your expression of interest in any job opportunity. Providing this information is strictly voluntary, and if you choose not to provide this information you will not be subject to any adverse treatment or action.

Information gathered on co-hosted job posting pages (where jobs posted on other websites are pulled in and displayed on NaijaJobsLink.com using iFrames) may become the property of NaijaJobsLink.com and the other company. In such cases, we are not responsible for that company’s use of your personal or demographic information, and the use of such information by the other company will be subject to the privacy statement of that company.

Personal Information on Job Seeker Profiles and Resumes

Information job seekers provide during the registration process will automatically be transferred to your online Profile. You will be asked to upload a copy of your resume and provide additional information to compete your Profile including, but not limited to, contact information, work history, education, and skills all of which is optional.

NaijaJobsLink.com provides you the following options regarding the accessibility of your online Profile:

  1. If you allow your Profile to be “Public”, portions of your Profile, but not your contact information or resume, may be accessible to the public. However, only registered employers and recruiters, will have access to your contact information and resume file.
  2. You can create a “Private” Profile and store your resume in our database without allowing it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your Profile or resume to be searchable means that employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product, but you can use it to apply for a job online.
  3. If you apply to a job posting on NaijaJobsLink.com and have a “Private” Profile and resume, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to access your contact information.

By visiting NaijaJobsLink.com, signing in to your account and navigating to My NaijaJobsLink and then My Profile, you can choose to make your Profile “Public” or “Private”. We strive to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to paying hiring managers, headhunters, employers, recruiters, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies as required by law, but cannot guarantee that third parties will not gain access to this database.

We are not responsible for the use made of our clients’ resumes by third parties who access resumes while they are in our searchable database. The portions of your searchable Profile (not your contact information) that are publicly available on NaijaJobsLink.com are accessible to any visitor. You may, at any time, edit any information in your Profile. If you would like to cancel your account and remove your Profile from NaijaJobsLink.com, please [contact us](http://naijajobslink.com/contact/).

Use of Web Beacons

If you post personal information in public areas of NaijaJobsLink.com, including but not limited to online forums or message boards, or in the NaijaJobsLink.com searchable resume database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you make available or post in public areas of NaijaJobsLink.com.

Posting Information in Public Areas of NaijaJobsLink.com

Any webpage on NaijaJobsLink.com may contain electronic images known as “web beacons” or “single-pixel gifs” that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personal information; they are a process used to compile aggregated statistics about our web Site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including time and date of a page view, a cookie number, and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides.

Users may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

Use of Cookies

A “cookie” is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. We use cookies to help maximize and personalize your online experience. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you, and are uniquely assigned to your computer.

The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, and as a convenience feature designed to save you time. For example, if you personalize NaijaJobsLink.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as your user name, password, and preferences). By using cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized Site experience. When you return to NaijaJobsLink.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

Your computer may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can generally modify your browser setting to reject all cookies. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is delivered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to reject cookies, however, be advised that performance may be compromised with a negative impact on your experience on NaijaJobsLink.com.

Modification of, and Access to, Your Information

You may at any time correct, review, update, or change your Account or Profile information by signing in and navigating to My NaijaJobsLink. From your My NaijaJobsLink Account or Profile you may also opt out of receiving email, newsletters and certain other information from NaijaJobsLink.com.

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of NaijaJobsLink.com more efficient, practical and relevant. At any time you can delete your Profile from NaijaJobsLink.com’s online database and/or close your NaijaJobsLink.com Account, in which event we will remove all copies of your resume, profile information and/or account information, except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet.

Security of Your Personal Information

We make a very reasonable effort to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those efforts or use your personal information for improper purposes.

When you place an order online at NaijaJobsLink.com, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. We use a service company to process its credit card transactions. For further information on this company’s privacy and security practices.

Children

NaijaJobsLink.com is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

Changes to Privacy Policy

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, so you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time.

If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy for NaijaJobsLink.com, we will notify you via email and/or will publish a change notice on the Site so that users will be informed of what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

Contact Information

Your data is submitted to NaijaJobsLink, through NaijaJobsLink.com and is hosted and stored in a database on our servers

NaijaJobsLink, LLC, a Lagos based company with its principal place of business at 1, Kola Ogunjale Street, Iyana Ipaja, Lagos, Nigeria, is the legal entity determining the purposes and means of processing the information gathered on the Site and is the data controller of all data stored in the NaijaJobsLink.com database.

If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://naijajobslink.com/contact/).
